[{"topicId":"13","id":"13000","langCode":"en","question":"Rkn3bJHZ4hqlzulccbneTxnVMvbBcVZq/id4fC6BNAsR0OXcXk9B6nNjrrQgJWNxv/qnCs26LtRxJ0AStUVnjA\u003d\u003d","answers":["have","had","has","hadn’t"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3E9vjJ7DGTLkyfkcMiGvBlVZyHPAiejrxLQrwU+ZaHv1w7wgVCCK2NuXV/VGH1Kx4EdjQCEbLn0k6iYQ3c6PTcTphVPxCNwDm0NkIzfKhULKced20omsaTxfMsskY/x+atLobz18JkmeWfnAsU2TMD/8y3GP+eyxE0wVWjXL4hIjC695kx1qoptSUEJEI0nsRdkhi2Ct4qMv+Iayot/7ASI\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13001","langCode":"en","question":"w+Tt5HFWg3KmtwkB7pJE8xvH+T3sQ+P931ONTt+O1zFxoGrR8rT8VZMmywAz7fha0Yse6NP7oEBvJoqux0rtuXTR06STGIwWVoWIcxeb45Y\u003d","answers":["has","had","have","haven’t"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3F8UepfSOmVvA7r2YEOBIQf+cGFW7ZeLTVopTYWQ7ykl6rCZalTjC4L4HctueJc5Vh5oVNUEhklZ+riiAYM4bm/uO+31ihVn75s15sYAGk7MQJjSkyAIyfm324eolTHkhlNOJ9tyZAIQGlvuArT3yGXoQAS2nwgokXlAADP5i3RtQR+4n46f+ublE31Pwzwcy2ZM03pe+ibDss04f47O+UU\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13002","langCode":"en","question":"NBj6Kly5ChoVLBHll18GAN9CES1lpPHcp11soKHcab14jMc7Qq1zB8ZbsEeQot1PlFCH14inUQIiLyaP9Vqo787CFxIuuHFGeqncpaTbAGhDrz9UM30j1mRBLUod+SH8","answers":["has","hadn’t","have","had"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"UAyNyciqQAXaQLsr3a1avEx6Y6QWGRFlCkAs42PkZOlxgPePNOMjlXSUV9yQCs5gfBfWjunn3HNnqjXJMQGAKk3pFmmPkWaBKfMS/GrHWx/IRCaBI/s69fxS3C2EkxCHbJzF50i11WzZE7pP2787TJqyOCa/WSuwjvKE+gMzIcb78JKmSOiIKrjODHKb3s/NbjFgGFLNROwPhU8O4GlR6ioE0QMzGrN0CCE9KPeyf5w\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13003","langCode":"en","question":"cCPgZANrhoCWMtBF4T7cRv/fGkMh0VHXqnizp28KjF1eELmkw1Aqv3MX2nTEipK5vSHfVhx0k4UTXsZ3ZiRbrD80g2F8z6oEPg5qDFpl6scCE8B0YVo9a2D9MNjgzcGQ","answers":["hadn’t","have","has","had"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"whtZUTiIGUOKx48ZaYaz7bbuZjgdfrQ53qi2/D7pTN3nFQry2XOHJ2cIbb73ySQCsvbxoV5cCVfBM8kXHYB2bhrXWYBPaPKNJg02TBrYH5TJChMFl8y6KH4b9DvsuKOmyDRuWcEqBrP0fgbC72D5sOYWzmjnRSGv4YuNPUMORumzWw3WYY5KyyNzK51R4yGrmMnGbIhfBFHgVklJqjHeng\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13004","langCode":"en","question":"J8TqUO7MRcsGIFXvKsGrHdqZHenATtoXEiUq5Kvb3XGysvRO1qp0ORwbIOnBPKYOBQATqYvSylno3Svh7WYTyOMepodorFUEhX4M7hpw3W4\u003d","answers":["has","had","have","hadn’t"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"whtZUTiIGUOKx48ZaYaz7bbuZjgdfrQ53qi2/D7pTN2MYgeUbfI6kGV7V4COaNMBzqEUUWNSo1iWYZ8aT1iOBfQKppEM3WZiqXWrK35+sUWjuHa3eeQ2Tudnf2eNdzt49Bjw+WoyRptcbEbJt0Fw/RPwkfNlilX0st1NoPJ+0KcYw7/VJUNAZRxkRtjIH0UGXDxd6tcut3zbXRyp92kzq2oezgUPFmsbCEk2D+6Rtg+2z3ZvmYBpy5BpGy4tvRO7"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13005","langCode":"en","question":"MABgjxsF/jHsYTWSVK5RepjM72EpaaGr9eeUXxdLFnKOg0Ax2UwMnMmqx3OKtAPpE17dFAOH+tH8IiG2P8grIg\u003d\u003d","answers":["had","have","hasn’t","has"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"whtZUTiIGUOKx48ZaYaz7bbuZjgdfrQ53qi2/D7pTN2MYgeUbfI6kGV7V4COaNMBzqEUUWNSo1iWYZ8aT1iOBfQKppEM3WZiqXWrK35+sUWjuHa3eeQ2Tudnf2eNdzt49Bjw+WoyRptcbEbJt0Fw/RPwkfNlilX0st1NoPJ+0KcYw7/VJUNAZRxkRtjIH0UGXDxd6tcut3zbXRyp92kzq2oezgUPFmsbCEk2D+6Rtg+2z3ZvmYBpy5BpGy4tvRO7"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13006","langCode":"en","question":"Aad+ETgRe52/mi+K5uip2JtJ2liLs+wZj+9LhczQSKTQ3thTxZ9KGnSiJ2ei9s2J35DKYJheLkn924voAYGzUA\u003d\u003d","answers":["has","have","haven’t","had"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"DnREY1GEE4yrkXhL5GVoIc0OCFObWdwkjx9685qCU8xuuadCVv7W9beX9LM4XU5Ye/RATwLRro2SNrpEOvQo2sxDd9FDVGIi6CCBLgXOj9ebA114HbZsqv36EMp51KBTaLHCQ7rHXJ4HOQQyuOh6mv4+a9OuRq1995FKDrIxO2VehfsP91GjgoEnBzntPOPlpA8/KnRHfa4Rgq4piXmWz99lUVCFyJ3HGTleOAqMwS/aClFSCLVwi9hCdRWKSJ4bFb7MDqBS8cS1xd8ndMGP+dOf/0rbJVWfHpHFd/NqGDkAp5VxIBfs2SczDyEmFvkyt7wGIYaspl5Piizdf181ew\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13007","langCode":"en","question":"Uf3hYw0asFTNM1OPu2X6Bo1gx8d0d6G2NUFPDd6pPTs/cV4CDgzZR8Ef5+u+5id4r1DpeK7L65RkLSWh407woqwm3ye+mGYmUsmYcklJHZARrRJSTf20qMxwy0JyhAUWXSKhgWTV/PdchdEEM0D8BA\u003d\u003d","answers":["doing","do","does","did"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"8j+B6dNinV6FU2ISaNoMBNAxMWtEzeKrdr89GGIGC19ft358bXg5QvRQ0tyx8j2LcCvpCfmymKNvyWjB6HZPxTmUE5VWEQmrf3+cd0Aw9Lnkj40T8nFZui4S4z7ShltEFibaITxppXs+eehPpF9rRv570dVpwLluVrS1KvrpRXymI5Ji3442h1VZjjVRXwBsi17SeMDqVKfnkok1velvJiUPjhR+FaYq6H5rQG8qCQuQ432p60NlSwbAn/nl14vevG9ZDUOis9U48ZPoYJnkrDpNYJXFFqE6oYX865Q1wYgZYGx0UAsazUGsygMVefGzjfr/QAKXcxHN8FzjRi4P1lyrOvpJJi3jfYJV/9Ydd7VhaornY1Rjgo1B7as6YGqb7dGW8dvP+C+VY9Bm8H3HMA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13008","langCode":"en","question":"4YCKwFyccEPJrCpSL96uuL+/AD1pk7iYoGarJ4ARA+KHSoIYgLRVBm54VI642C5VcR1sJ12qc+UWQ5FOj/M+9Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["doing","do","does","did"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"sV4mhKCZ+w+CwWH9trKNXYstVo1FWyznn6VD0owaeZLOui2huOtxhQgPQuM10SZmEOWZ9ZrPEXHlXkfPNxl7AAtrAetdENiF50H59uGr//xGXrH2UzSZihFcYeL7XNR7NRUobxrqhjxkNmm9SoziwWZrV96Ze/lxAqVG+08tAOY1stjRH20G9EK3ZTs7ZPuG0gPOtwmyuxw44gwOUj4tlqo3KjyfD6xlUyL7gQlB9w466TF0B+Rm7xdAonrcTnUXw215HdGA0O4AHw8Ji7WyP1/jSSPLJD8G7OVat0x7ots\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13009","langCode":"en","question":"WwEQRDwrvwwHc853Zsrx6H2/dVOBaRf4Gf/Bzv7HM9B5R4R58NL0zV7UOuJfRB9r","answers":["didn’t","don’t","did","doesn’t"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"vCFvIPVeqPVntrvVgmEx+/C2qCzqSwYqHhoaQ2lRhmf3wa9asJD0p8nlVM676ktUjKpJq6g/JA8YQik+hWzkIy7jSFSvnZ1V08SsQFW6lsnKMGzC2pI3yTgpKL20OqtVidZlfZJBG0pFE70C8HVq/3fKO0MGohJhgxCTqAbPFbDHr60VXJG+61PtVkgXJB6IWP9Mb7nXJGbmJ1IPZXLDKDGD7I675/ZgGY+aKaEl3Q1zYZVbDS1TIXSjC4XUb1U1TYj8gUzkfNIhN6mMvY0Bjn1BcqrUM8xii6Sul4x6O9pBH7ifjp/65uUTfU/DPBzLx/kCcR6Nn0jXOJs09g0xNg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13010","langCode":"en","question":"BDTvg/eLY5IfhNl9glh219NyXRuiGGy8xeJR4PvRV0ON+d6nLiH+c30X7c8G/k/BZgTe7xTAiyXEWOkbTewG4g\u003d\u003d","answers":["does","do","did","doing"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"IlIqy4Luw6ugNAACrRN74vBBZvGOG32ZYBhp/Q6qCztn79DtignLClo6pucuCjV7Q/WUbcSDlJK0YWpOj7g1APBEzTRcjoZwtS9mS1JPFDqpAmvXeWOYPKQ/mDJuUNxnzEE9tDTrqZ/STR4ITVNEUrbjtRLVJxXcXkd1Z8a2cA/G2lTOqlRAwqIbggCozZ2UuwFzwnvFs19KdSiMTWM9e6CBdvpQcMzsd2+J5/7cdz7Vt6NGB5dO1NtHG448dz3UZYGYQOapWqJFxdF8Z0urHdaISHmKTudK1OwcSXmMdqNHWvXiwjiFxumKVQEtXaZwah7OBQ8WaxsISTYP7pG2D15+344IBVJZ6GKvVkkeRUM\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13011","langCode":"en","question":"60gkHpVMGXEJ58UL0lGFxEn8sfL+ZknylTkBB6W9CG+ewerUwd46EsRuCHgmrbny","answers":["don’t","did","does","do"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"vCFvIPVeqPVntrvVgmEx+/C2qCzqSwYqHhoaQ2lRhmf3wa9asJD0p8nlVM676ktUjKpJq6g/JA8YQik+hWzkIy7jSFSvnZ1V08SsQFW6lsnKMGzC2pI3yTgpKL20OqtVidZlfZJBG0pFE70C8HVq/3fKO0MGohJhgxCTqAbPFbCVou8qaYzSeE+mRniSH9U8xfBZ2UZVnbRRJTdprYwSueBg5Ugv/9Ta4i4jB28UiB9b2RNGu3LkS4+fM3SC6BlPSKoYzSrBudIgTF4eIlurQNOf/0rbJVWfHpHFd/NqGDkAp5VxIBfs2SczDyEmFvkydZnWHnjLphtPdwmQyZE0qA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13012","langCode":"en","question":"EKUIrwbQ03BmTjQgv50IVxzZObqN1zdSKvXL06RkFfbLAi4LjssCsORhGgqrrveICFOxCupc1FwlrCZByQRUGEOIGl/+z0JmeKufLh3lw38\u003d","answers":["did","does","do","don’t"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"czA4NWlKAnNDifPxx3QNDdLG9VdFCnkxE5P+hhyn7pzoFr1U2uSiEzcr7AjhJWkvG0gSMZYay7fhUCAB10K8t+/X0Qpr6RXH9jyXPwqf/PsCfDP68r+rVjdymXcqd46vkkjGJd+GRLj3VwMiLIoFT0ah8Y0kdBPBrookPKd2dCVTWxlxAqfdYa0Bj5WZTnpG1lXv7yXDUOL2FSIxl4eMnoRvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13013","langCode":"en","question":"F12CdfkZy8cyaNnQIgY4AUcQJ26RdqZdvSpX5SB/b8QRMiW4AI3as3qaJ9hY5M1+","answers":["did","do","does","doing"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3ALV8VAXiwo0bAVMtZqfaTHYmeYHFFlPf1N9dtGT6ldpO85v6lVGtFb2Nxjw2BYg3NMk3XPmauMKkl9WuMN+B4Z9QXKq1DPMYoukrpeMejvat6dMSyJrslLPtsIhlWEyg7VVDg3Yo9ro6rngSmU6Xxk\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13014","langCode":"en","question":"FM2xVRu123j+KdqyJ55y78oZ6OzV7SOajtXYJ4wRYLLgavasPBbUnhr2GID8zbhB","answers":["don’t","did","does","do"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3ALV8VAXiwo0bAVMtZqfaTFjxHBYNjwxmJ2h6/JvQvPOHq+gqJah830lkR9kvSVmj/qLhjnJYWUreCo6rzcmBsIg/hQWiciSQbA8bI6lE1lBCCN7av4nCiiW3uUxukiNHPqr0MY+Z9m9OGWWT+c+mgIGC7oOZ74qijwTTs2ZOti7"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13015","langCode":"en","question":"5++guFzOKQxwqzmXzg/4J/wumTkKaW04OQxr2vGCs+o3A9148Mt+ZocEcXFPs4mh","answers":["doesn’t","do","does","did"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"6DNG4oNyk1YL6x020kreNIrl99e7f8JZ1ukbsRC+dByLOCmBwTrats5PAdbQGsPI5b5W4ZDSPebSGfE7KVz0q8JnhlPPwEJdkFi+NWcTiN0qCvCR9XpbqJjUr4x87BgRnU8lgAsapfyTZWIuUl495LGnWx6b8jz7iJm/O3TYQjj4n+N/5Vd7cj7Eeed0UHXX374NCfEqNAO8dsWqth3Y17geuvX3W4a1sXHcAWtYL/jYSBJM+YQiXSc52nYpGwMyFF/5lDwHWs4XNnVFYF3x5yTjr3TeURfI2Q/pO74WGc59QXKq1DPMYoukrpeMejva6iLr0uRNDhpgzT8YNcjLjrVVDg3Yo9ro6rngSmU6Xxk\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13016","langCode":"en","question":"z61t0Vw7NOS1yWM+FVU1ThAb4loMFjN5m6kts6TzqHQiwTXt77hOegOKUKc30edM","answers":["doesn’t","don’t","does","do"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"KjZx7+HMDSMtCHaHA8MD+izJtACYwmTBKG1c7U3SfVbAmH4QFxBHeFSFWTzSWGWUKr9sy96vFVMZboTJJvgCcFx/JMsTnMTJoznJkYu/oatK9RpoRpaFxDNQnm/+qM4VI/Wz9fxdC7bu4ipIioVXDFuqnxVwsiDCytDda5TFbz2XUuhYoBSPZn1kenmy23Mwezt2nx3jYK2B0oGfKSCE3rehLPcS/LxxZOsQPcS+aXw\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13017","langCode":"en","question":"OqdrvTWxP80KItDKssgsVlBlOqSUgDEyisAcPWhoJ2G4PMQsuKm5GNOFa/4qm8vOXg1x994mF0XKqypHg5AlM/z4ECPlZwnyWkUvdTiDSE8\u003d","answers":["don’t","must","mustn\u0027t","do"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"7TYJFILHV9Jem4SD6ubyJrq4q4QBH43reqGdqJ9wNSlZMLMuRou+dl3d2LYE/yzbl0Ql1BBP858KgWiMGcC7Xxwl1Oc10pCpxJ2lGiCzqVxqHs4FDxZrGwhJNg/ukbYPX9jYumXQcn3UEC5JFOpujg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13018","langCode":"en","question":"Wj2+L7z/5Ejc5eWxEstMEJq9/L9U/eKvPa+L8HVyawBfLqzjc74rIfn0KF4v4fFEuwXe3zjTwREnroYynH+bmJpRvG0ZWDvw2r30DKDgvRTyggM/CgKS0mWC5x36S7MV","answers":["will","must","mustn’t","won’t"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"7TYJFILHV9Jem4SD6ubyJrq4q4QBH43reqGdqJ9wNSlZMLMuRou+dl3d2LYE/yzbl0Ql1BBP858KgWiMGcC7Xxwl1Oc10pCpxJ2lGiCzqVxqHs4FDxZrGwhJNg/ukbYPpqZK0MswJknSbq6dKQxCnA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13019","langCode":"en","question":"j/NcxBo/ifQ1cCrDEJTReM/SAyGs3RJcfwZFDs7hzo2s+Acx60JTl7ee9AcFarenLvNOCy6RWl9FZjkE25OZQw\u003d\u003d","answers":["do","does","don’t","doesn’t"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"KjZx7+HMDSMtCHaHA8MD+izJtACYwmTBKG1c7U3SfVbAmH4QFxBHeFSFWTzSWGWUKr9sy96vFVMZboTJJvgCcFx/JMsTnMTJoznJkYu/oatK9RpoRpaFxDNQnm/+qM4VI/Wz9fxdC7bu4ipIioVXDFuqnxVwsiDCytDda5TFbz2WNl1w9+ymP2AteTCsAwz+NR8IlU2j4WGo7Kq1w69xKgabICeoD2AxFQ8MECmQg/UO2VSzMjZbn7SI0gVi8JIFhRc4zog9o+EXRiXuT4/Spw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13020","langCode":"en","question":"DqkhbaJP2hv/+C8eV4Q6kM+5UtTsrjtPrtwaoqmZjL+PLPVhXAdNCQkbAAPB7Plagq4XtlmOHy2ALy0c7GLQ4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["should","have","does","will"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"iMwoCjbVJ3wyfH1rEVEDitwMnLXBHyhINMNAAa9n8V060KumJnQalqqPRh+/nTaHpR2k2Kc5k7qbygpdihJmYWboe0DrnwLIYuixmtpNC8w5BWeFmqyaeNcAAMJyU/FoWaFHSOkhH5uOPBbo5Rk19fURb8JqVQ3YfuIia63R4oA\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13021","langCode":"en","question":"e4zMhC74b4oz4GFz/pjJyJ6kYVU+PnHTCnJhklQ7qYVk2/c7wbXwBrtC5ErbJVyigGmRLNWReioKZ6D2G+v9ixU34fGSksI9wyIvwh4tN4UDgNLEOGWvCOlrUO0x0Ar4","answers":["will","should","won’t","shouldn’t"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"iMwoCjbVJ3wyfH1rEVEDitwMnLXBHyhINMNAAa9n8V060KumJnQalqqPRh+/nTaHpR2k2Kc5k7qbygpdihJmYWboe0DrnwLIYuixmtpNC8w5BWeFmqyaeNcAAMJyU/FoWaFHSOkhH5uOPBbo5Rk19fURb8JqVQ3YfuIia63R4oA\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13022","langCode":"en","question":"EnovdZGXg/xRUpmu5dQlyu8ycUG4ejGwsjtJETO/noOrJF4XWGO2vGcBeGfk57TJavfscGSxzWh3TEwuSTWX6VSAvsI62zeaaNO8jJscDhE\u003d","answers":["should","will","would","wouldn’t"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"LIZBE3/WGdjr5zloFeqmla6QvZImneCvQyvevIqUaBCNCuBGSEcLCu0K0foiFagUDMjp4X1VtfeDfhshIzbqMenVplJKoxMY1blkdb5j9DT0p3m5kjqG9ZYUOjiUWFlLDPAoEAPyF/fcpyG0qqrr8yB5E7ae9A18vmH6Fi8lKWg\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13023","langCode":"en","question":"dQzOLXmo+KIRyJAWOLu9aZ9rTMKtFsiKx4qd8JDPWUSNOnrHyDb2pZY+A7avhPkZGOgDBJ2A5DNPfGT78BdNAA\u003d\u003d","answers":["was","is","are","were"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"haymPDckd+aWWvS4OcPuBc6AJxlmN5cNKdFIZKFQ+qZLExT2HFRsJ0RzCjiXniGH4SXLPAEx2s/Pc/VYjINlEWc+aawcXB669L3Gsb8U4kMYbhgi8UrLPv2dvJjnXfYXDW0Fa6r1AT5WqRZQn8RhnGjjUunlyKXznqNVSJmlnScSbUHMJrJyAcVxEYWi3k2iB+RSRymt81WxZi8fLnrAUFcXyuYqBmR64TJj42o7DTI\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13024","langCode":"en","question":"8JpF+O+5WrDZLfQ0LdHInOZjz/i7blajsbF/J4ZICGmhCRB6E8HB58sPDDRHey77","answers":["will","should","shouldn’t","won’t"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"vCFvIPVeqPVntrvVgmEx+/C2qCzqSwYqHhoaQ2lRhmf3wa9asJD0p8nlVM676ktUjKpJq6g/JA8YQik+hWzkIy7jSFSvnZ1V08SsQFW6lsnTVwP6W/tW+8pEyhdzM0qlzvlNgJm06v2ZymwUT9bsfrZH3EE28TZ+Zt7gU08VDQQlcVlRM6VqOfduHTUog7aTCGb5IKfuOipd0paaB5AuhPlifzUiuQ1AqLwL1dRywBMR07Q3vw0ZcRiDBeE76sw1LP9IoTOkzFe9JZ2nAit8Aeh5I8fpCd3e2nAHDf+prKgAN56qepoVMv552I844cjBS1qimhYgSZrUtXDdQ8qi4A\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13025","langCode":"en","question":"l5wd4fs7hZZIfuEs/egGdi7Qt1v0CS+UbDvhlU17kKDPuxEVPguvao01g/uMymsPlzZy2BlBgzkrhgLWzx0hzg\u003d\u003d","answers":["has","do","have","did"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3LxKydtBfTigRsa2bOjEEr60wO5FYDHZBU2ruBR/AnbaRdk227GF7T4xsMH6cHr3xPkNEX5+YEz9tFOn5sbxYfK271EI9nfJJofvupqzjEX8wME7JoqqlUm25O5xlEc7t7os88zHh867eWsNebirNsY\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13026","langCode":"en","question":"OeyS4fXof+S5ISr4xghqpxEeTdolRv5XW25+uA/0mVInHPGAOkoN/OhmUOUOiuIdRWP35HOyI8VQpdUGLZvap070amLodZOsK9ZM6DPaIH5yVLP7Y6TKP49epyyn0pUE","answers":["am","was","were","is"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3L+MS0QP8E5gmxcey3f5rY3wnfCHxdPzRv9dmppFJhEXvNwGT9meNDCHT8pDN3AOqiFhGGS8Fk7zYRDZAQo7B6e2f4im4Y0tLIy5hB7k3WZgi17SeMDqVKfnkok1velvJrWKAlifLTSLF0BQVoJj37z0t4JjZabtOAdkzqcxsqq48JQnAj0QoeZ4FrJ3AS3+sH64ET+Ap1+xSRDd64k9xaYKtynICqBsihu1S9zkW1URltU6AIhEZLPawhrQjVQu53qOnIWpXiS0hQ1q8Qfmv8e6LPPMx4fOu3lrDXm4qzbG"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13027","langCode":"en","question":"VivWWGZHwQhpE/FjfPq22tOGzkQNKZh0yEb9MFZ6To1Ktm3aJm2qD8oHM5a95DzLhJApCgdIZOvbOEXL03ZeOL08CPiqosKt1SDo8HAQm2s\u003d","answers":["are","is","has","have"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3LiOhMAIT+PXVlWEYspSgLjwX1H69RzfN2rxK3gEy8R8HFqjs6CPIcdCW5vFbBdYI8HByKMt67oKSEN807z8jSDLVBwiEVTpTF5u9taS8N8qDR0JKwE/rjNT9wwyDyekwyWIHWrL9btIqdkCiwmea+pEYRL9q6IVzRDSmtgIrCF2lTiNWMilCIgycaaZj2A8+Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13028","langCode":"en","question":"uAi00eGIsfsyjiME1aOs87h+TTZ2HunW+OGF3fLcMgrjEO8CpfayOhKSPuY2Jj7OHS1FhhhyOLOuGK5A+eHkpX6PTLjd807iABrzsEEunSQIy2j36wL9Xkw9OZaJHt+PB3+AtFzfqfU1C3f0sjKp0A\u003d\u003d","answers":["are","is","was","were"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3JNVT4nIMhulU9Bld1zSxtHOEuv7PUzwaOySs3BeYCnUGTGAipnKMoSWbRW/9ZwIR8FVan+mNWa24iJWmtRah0hiU62xekY988wh4YiLI48B2vFyuI/OpTLblHxxR58BTBwbyGYEuSr9Y8AEsmkdVkbhv0P955o2jojV51EKQKI5LaiKV5ln3prKv51mdLsNjw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13029","langCode":"en","question":"lzdD8st0Idf0fKYTDHqOQUvLxD/XcqkNk1SISC3XvI9Vxu+7kAukRCiOW+d6h8CP7jm84Kgm144aOx2R0SO3EQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["have","do","does","has"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3B5NmcMA2FgkArZ58jY2Hqu3ANqB+hw0S08GP0isj5aZXMpTz84MJB6gnr3SOplM+DZ+5WzfDk/YqTetFBcTv+VbgY8MX8odp+Lw87HgbxQ0dcjh9076Xdr7KctzvFcSEkMNECdcyyA6dtOOpwhFDsRwgCNmQZBd1Kf3o54buDjxEK/qvRBollI/xcjIAe8TSg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13030","langCode":"en","question":"qe9Sp65MukfJ/nY95t5GqL3dXt6+FINkaA5anrNHDOyjPCWrneB3J7vsB+yMc3BBS2dACtRJiqj5YcCV/Spu0QrNMziNs2/C9dx3++eE+2Q\u003d","answers":["am","is","will","are"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"F0ed7rsc6G1yvqJEbZO3EdCjn9w8EAyfgu5Fo4ttYdeWqbMqQLU2kkeNEAedkEY7/nqwPrX2nfdfdWu3XIr3QNnk0LDaxvyPzSo5rCx0uJI2fuVs3w5P2Kk3rRQXE7/lR0kRdeyFLyXhI4hokU6fxnXI4fdO+l3a+ynLc7xXEhJDDRAnXMsgOnbTjqcIRQ7EgkopILmt0YjDEImZVgFt5EjTZzmOJX3xoqNmHuw1K2I\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13031","langCode":"en","question":"O9sGGKOL/0ImlwDzGVXL267cp0VJDp5uH1h71E52fW3E2ogHDl4+kRubOhl/QBhw","answers":["hadn’t","has","had","have"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"ephe6H6AY8t3fxNGjHMUU7mmZ41Pxin8OJZw+k5F8ehl2iwL5B5T53v4xkMGyvnksBfj5BJj5F19YFcHJG0WFID7Sh3Iiwwyd52Rc8O/LZccWqOzoI8hx0Jbm8VsF1gjwcHIoy3rugpIQ3zTvPyNIIMviPD15JpBluwTOMvXxTl7O3afHeNgrYHSgZ8pIITeVK2h8v02GXo/bsT2QaiiGQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13032","langCode":"en","question":"9vQKPRaWeZ8qo9byObiKFTLeCMzRyq75MvFT4UJb4axO/6iQTS3+goiOtV4tangxBjDEnW3GTquLtcAV7UKJgtkLsd6LGkLUJtbJ50sDSrFcAtu/LI+zdqSwkW+/f5tN","answers":["is","was","were","are"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"lBVjEUELtutXyTX26w1l/jGrprXyMZuSy+j7zjwKC+1dRAtWtw2llJlAxQg7LjWA6tVPVpOtT0Gv0Ipjvak1o1w/PbeHcVLlIjKKZWDzDnO3VXW9CY00xtQNgNd/WDZHnbl1zzPiCfSbPoHm1llMvBwGFi+A43NZ+l737+Gw4rOOsie8VVtAxVRSNwC6E2fUkHW/2UNwexUTs6xZKNZ7CA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13033","langCode":"en","question":"2LqzN7z4PsAnTeF6TPbVHbgqwhhfvoJSRXADK8vlZgrKKFu2ORE0KXl77EX5NjpXOeQM+GFEAIdHaiueA9v4A92AQP9J+1PdAKtFhiXzb0g\u003d","answers":["hadn’t","has","have","had"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"umTR/DsZ2PqxdkH9koRM/xNvhqIUUwRZ8lhnKjwMZD44NeVv5Ynto6eJivPOL5D0BpDWBqO2XPxtpjSPj50mboPa1G7vcL8ygFcByZA6T8u2yEiZOUmZQwqd6VRQfwYDwj5+eKNsj87akTVKkaH5hARpYl4pKS3w/S4yCwtMchks8W+7f+N3y8BBBRa9dEKc6m9nAoVbjZgWzizpWFVYH5Eep+EJMRz5sWrGG6mLvTESmuTYWgxoiqGI3qHmOfDzezt2nx3jYK2B0oGfKSCE3hCv6r0QaJZSP8XIyAHvE0o\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13034","langCode":"en","question":"gAgcjWp3lLBPiRAU+WMlKVPow1lGUMneT8rJlk7cH3TP2t6M0HjUY4gHYmwfEWvk4mNltMV9Pw43OqPgrnEdiA\u003d\u003d","answers":["has","have","hadn’t","had"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"UAyNyciqQAXaQLsr3a1avACO/VI3Jdo8+M3614YLSTd/iToWCcXrAUWoZG1Kke5jG4OSG49KJExI7cptM7v3MSSMnv0p2WuY7CXhXNVUY3aLACJM5AL4VE2XGCEHrSqsbj9bF+snFWS7xR0KW1fH+jO/2dKvLxDDbRbzSsRb6SRYCPRtrQdin0fcgKBf69On"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13035","langCode":"en","question":"mcWBSZ2pBclnLINNhlCci3whYdm2U/YPu+WJb630hBjAksHu00mTHwvAScElRFsVXG/Bix7G7wH25vSH/fd0YQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["won’t","will","should","would"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"UAyNyciqQAXaQLsr3a1avPCKknCV5qyaYoNgN3GPaF+KsVcBWtZ6QT+K//BbjNRbZVyt6PW7hU6KJXwec7ggePauRQSo148glktzYbkwWW7slqRhPOpf8OOKtU0ZPUiv4Rolib/Z6OcxFsOlKWgIm2qJWjuPfexflfWu4eGc+9G0uNk2wvj3RM1BQhbsTN0AhjbGENCDohmxK2IMmvAwzhuvg2CoR7zAG/CqjdL4LkRftHjFZ9SeMxSqVFhu2kbcFYgy3fiI3OVG6DYXdSG6P5oTeqXM9FtTDCYTRgVWUaFTAQ0VtqWfn7olrxGknEfFw215HdGA0O4AHw8Ji7WyP/NSgna3GzfhqKxHufIkHAs\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13036","langCode":"en","question":"AaRZ6cRhlO3pyfiAnudCSWkr3luyYCDKozaO3dwMZyXzbIs+BkxzKnhq4xgDF9eGUCdNoZkLqIwwW9QePAQqrX2+zdCR/isI2DuVXtVGMO9UgL7COts3mmjTvIybHA4R","answers":["won’t","will","wouldn’t","would"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3Dyu+0do396l8h7AFygdaxBW0ssMapzjDyXNmdcqx/hD9XvZKlKwbsLsWqYBEnuua5xRIqjOgtFWO4K2UMshiVc7zm/qVUa0VvY3GPDYFiDcGNn+XhPGNp1ZTADUfmxRAujchPuY/YxKprHVWY9G/Z3fZyucF/k8c1ZVCedGREj5EkVrfjjuVb4tMNHIldivN0n6Td2h0yOri7bqxOH3GVUTpsY1Dp0IGqTEYxBDfuHHfCbWlxzy7EvvnCJdn5EAGtYYWv8l4d7qm0x82o5kUdtMXZjf67YnraQ5SN00utaCGtrX0y6levOTmXX9piKd6OgD5j88kQ5zxxRgrbkaVh44E//x/95bTwzMG5UfeanH"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13037","langCode":"en","question":"9UQdR4BbFNTq3zLsytXgg1wwOZGwZ0Jf2Sb6NW8T9FZPDpnpPOD3QPMO+ujKHo6wRDeoWdOObQOQdE54iuQmAeEbuUZjz94vRNdQ/QYhnf3ZcQQB8v8tSUonVT7GOvQv","answers":["are","does","do","is"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"LIZBE3/WGdjr5zloFeqmlX7r8o20SfGa0hvFzVjowKucXngz2VdCpNNFGPRy0bbvRhYTOOIJ80aVSG3h863KCcpZMCRIlE04zfz0BrL/dYReier5g9KpqRodpNKlgPRNCQVPQN9hDxmqbTAwPFRi4UVyv87zfxvEAwakAnIy5iFqHs4FDxZrGwhJNg/ukbYPkSJM+Fl3tuUUmlMUCGh5dw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13038","langCode":"en","question":"99qqjUzJCRpDBU13ZQszx2FUGPJfFmkRYa4JiBDsCWvsyvDFiotJCZbml4GA6zsPA1qPWsHDWzBQnWAyjh/Bog\u003d\u003d","answers":["were","weren\u0027t","was","wasn’t"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"8WYexw//1b5cwdfeaQrGy/pqCTcKigFRcNRnoo/XGcFpc2zp1LR7t6cXCRSMYt8eHLZIOjM0Y48nj55R1URtMnGoLGcCLLr5Sg3EdeM92bM+hff0kruOqeYY042vzEhmOe+H48k9K9mfS+mZfKE+K8kRXdZXf1UmIXyxeRxQ3pMBMYmWLJMIOeKixhMCPAzW"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13039","langCode":"en","question":"vFkrTA/IKy/KD8y0+RIqy/54WPPaDYm2Clt3O8z31ot7WunZLBwLkaLJXJjGM2M/","answers":["am","do","are","is"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3ALV8VAXiwo0bAVMtZqfaTFjMquyYSGGOA8PIAffh3lJz8MjG8V/Au90Zt61h+iF1NzO43Bqk8LMD+8/lAav3rDmiF4VC8ajJZKYL4dscR1a"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13040","langCode":"en","question":"4dHvcHeIZfumRsImIKoZoYy1jiPGfOQ+vQlGxQJz1XF6uU/LfoZxYs+wj76hupmqyLDkg1F75T8FA9op0fDr1YTRs+ETA2c7d9TiKRfhuIY\u003d","answers":["hasn’t","has","hadn’t","had"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3HOKWDnjt+214GybfNyVzmQeRL4bQhwhMhZltcQt0bkY0qAO861pxal/2XNlyttnHzlgCxCiuK232IfgkwRtlUT/Woqmwb0RQzuhWD53Q6kfdKjaUukFAkbbK3exv3ROpU4cQ8lWWlzZ7+ClSth8BsW+xjXs9cknOB9QzfjsxKj8hVig6MeYI0ardiK79EKCsXWumrLzVjA4wtrcF+LDWQZrv6rUDyyBknbPMVxdbtwPH8mdRQspvhdZfZoTxQP6HvoCMqu0u3aBh9uRVS+ricW1VQ4N2KPa6Oq54EplOl8Z"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13041","langCode":"en","question":"3yfvSzOaArfLIVAxkqa6TzHNV/nf/6dXkoGtbbtL86KApt9IJdru5Avgzy4+x09yId99in03EO1bslclLRXr0g\u003d\u003d","answers":["is","are","was","were"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"eAjJ9m4GeG2R0U/sPX9t5oCzw9aItXGFMWJP0k1O35EiSw6NTYZXY7PDQkKPkO5IWXVaUQK0GdteUEW7SFPk7XBnpTHSwNoAzNCdP9PYB6n8G8r1nQ56aK6CGm0r1J2Tx4ChGGKf4utzIqHCyO2YTYR6spI4hW5PKAP+CYx32bbPkypI/NjOM+gFTk5fiDwofUFyqtQzzGKLpK6XjHo72rLG5a8avZd63IVztxOzIwW1VQ4N2KPa6Oq54EplOl8Z"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13042","langCode":"en","question":"xOaqDc9DybdNpZ5ox/oKyUI7ZVEOlfguSfRLxZdCfvoTngZlcXrBnNpbnvZATCBu","answers":["was","is","were","are"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"/4wvqV78ZLhnhbNN0JWBLlY/phqB4HhGhshZweFl/Euv5babK0peSI58BZnQtRWVU1JmkHjgCbPkN87Qojbu0AZqkH21y1+VnNw3we0PfNEXcvCzIHxYP3P63AS/rIOMjiY6jsA9/3nWAbTUgH5ejb52ohVOKccN/aN6sIxtkhefybY4UKsZTcBVjyl+Bf5oEFQMjSylfP+COGASHuENKP9OnxD2w3EBqIwO2ux2EYr1GmIpGW52eT344XgTEfBC/gzYDN4VZqCUBzLCVQ6SDNOf/0rbJVWfHpHFd/NqGDlMpsfZ/Rlru41SP114omyntVUODdij2ujqueBKZTpfGQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13043","langCode":"en","question":"gvE9PfglVZ9VaUtZWygw87lLnqNxXvHZ94uyslZd/mvy9bJjxvPhySNOcC20TcnJ96H7TTDK8ADZH6XbFEV+klRMbfGnxgCKzLR+Igftoyg\u003d","answers":["was","are","were","is"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"LIZBE3/WGdjr5zloFeqmlbwqQWO8cHLu1BGQQgK967Dsz54uzAVmQFacazDMk+ECDuOh8MKSo9+YEiyl+w8vcFdX4/LPqIFvRLl/KRTmRq1Gj0deQTHrr2acki0qD16i3aWOq7SVty9DiItbNhevurN9qbcsWuDVFyMdW4gvk40V646msDSLnUlbHDEF4UCwDtlUszI2W5+0iNIFYvCSBcCeVRAnUdCtol6GzJ7UXAg\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13044","langCode":"en","question":"yJEdFM4Q2YN4kVGJQGaktBSJlpHVEnMFdO645vG+D3UXX7JMZu/07q0T6oRCqBjnY1qbgfg9gYUrG54oVJX1Xw\u003d\u003d","answers":["is","are","was","were"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"haymPDckd+aWWvS4OcPuBYsys4UJnFwyECOL8x+SVLMKprK6/wPo+JMd9LO4A5M84SXLPAEx2s/Pc/VYjINlEWc+aawcXB669L3Gsb8U4kMYbhgi8UrLPv2dvJjnXfYXDW0Fa6r1AT5WqRZQn8RhnGjjUunlyKXznqNVSJmlnSceJ6N5KHPMrC9V6O71YGw0+/CSpkjoiCq4zgxym97PzeV9/bB5VHM8DiMpqOzfPsp3S69EfhTcjLA3KOOgBXRK"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13045","langCode":"en","question":"u2MqpOr3WuaqKxHrv9P9+Xp/8IDZm5a+DWPRasJOIKRTAlh3wAAfvsMzuR/P97jwOFB2kScsh/wiZkjmvK/FVTFJwRFsnwsjuehLro0ldlk\u003d","answers":["does","do","did","don’t"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"haymPDckd+aWWvS4OcPuBYsys4UJnFwyECOL8x+SVLMKprK6/wPo+JMd9LO4A5M84SXLPAEx2s/Pc/VYjINlEWc+aawcXB669L3Gsb8U4kMYbhgi8UrLPv2dvJjnXfYXDW0Fa6r1AT5WqRZQn8RhnGjjUunlyKXznqNVSJmlnScXfjfCXigKNFgB1A25lNgd+/CSpkjoiCq4zgxym97PzZrycIGZzxOV+6LU0UAg6iRN3JED07ZLuHI86mmK/O9k"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13046","langCode":"en","question":"0oSyK+9Z1MjgymEyo+6+Vw3uzwfxQQFPfduam/AA1eQFDMCw5f1EU0YF+oEtbiVf","answers":["was","is","are","were"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3FwXaCf4iZQ5tH4htYEWYTVFg5XCCEl+rxpxBgxFXTk7isRV5iC6GKdnRvFAXAaBTRxSpj82r4+OHiV2/v9Vz7zEcMt6AhUlrO3R/OOblDMAM43FHJWYg+7LCzgPMCZVcT7pn7qf9Tdh1kBZMnC9ado\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13047","langCode":"en","question":"reZ0vX9FfKlGafpxavFTh84wZ4RZV478TVfoa5s3WdNdtX3vKP/l6/8AETV2z8kMhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["is","was","are","were"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"haymPDckd+aWWvS4OcPuBc6AJxlmN5cNKdFIZKFQ+qYZEyJawOfF+Q0ABM9XJYzTesszfWC/ALS2ETWF1pdq2td0XppnUsUPtGOny27T7kOpOfDgzaFJdc9UffJyJI4No7htcyv2OeloY2sB9BO6VjXgznY4yCYZx7xz34JFv4WT/yJAbTzcodDGmTJg0hpEMY/Wd1OBhKDvYrWlQtI78w\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13048","langCode":"en","question":"WvT1LmUBJi39rzauiSXPQ6RZ1cebIgxMwNHY4uAsip8CNr7pKwJ63BZnt8DA0HzzFAaIXxFeYILcltvQLp727NTbbBvTm+7XFfxzSbXpSVaehFy0Rp+zM2j6YYi9r5W8","answers":["are","were","was","is"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"fbYUV1ZLKlcp62xprJGr3MTtQ4Et/IEBDq43F0Ieuw4yK3HQEcIQ1aRUJCtcnDdrDuOh8MKSo9+YEiyl+w8vcFdX4/LPqIFvRLl/KRTmRq1Gj0deQTHrr2acki0qD16i1FV0I9uakMab2XXKFwwWsmHjx26pZKmOXdtqHG4/EG1+qGJ6D9L2B8vjYB6gwN39XySUxKKXe6vqqwtfeWe/nwfkUkcprfNVsWYvHy56wFAoldDOwyBqo2TBWQxPzEsI"},{"topicId":"13","id":"13049","langCode":"en","question":"BZk9uw3x+fy4Z0cKvtlzgbBtiZi9Whep6y69PaHEFz+sG8A9uBAWZyrWwLSjcnSSZC8vPGELgxODE9tlO4yUERZNVNuL+KXvnyH6O/7knYBsYkaWksOATELkIJ8Z1qjV","answers":["can’t","must","mustn’t","can"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"eX9+C4ySmdcfgyAeTH5gAB06gY2E+QvKqjd92Tbxoyy2R/4n7s147nOZXGAsm7s+Ji/Qi0xS580FvdRUnuFv2TgfzdXebO1EtsRwCuoEkos1VbZX0mXgt2Jz/SuJ0YuYyrFLot6cii/5TdPaay5Kh6JGhU7F7dDhj+2yQSdBY7oUaJk3UbZys4QKtzp6xmfYhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d"}]